<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Monster Timer</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_description">This service monitors YouTube Shorts usage to help parents manage screen time. It detects when Shorts are being viewed and triggers a timer.</string>
    <string name="permission_overlay_title">Display Over Apps</string>
    <string name="permission_overlay_desc">Required to show the monster overlay when the timer expires.</string>
    <string name="permission_accessibility_title">Accessibility Service</string>
    <string name="permission_accessibility_desc">Required to detect when YouTube Shorts are being watched.</string>
    <string name="timer_label">Shorts Time Limit</string>
    <string name="pin_label">Parent PIN</string>
    <string name="monster_gallery_label">Monster Gallery</string>
    <string name="add_monster">Add Monster</string>
    <string name="remove_monster">Remove</string>
    <string name="save_settings">Save Settings</string>
    <string name="parent_unlock">Parent? Enter PIN</string>
    <string name="times_up">Time\'s up!</string>

    <!-- EULA -->
    <string name="eula_title">End User License Agreement</string>
    <string name="eula_text">MONSTER TIMER — END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT\n\nLast updated: February 2026\n\nPlease read this agreement carefully before using Monster Timer.\n\n1. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS\nBy installing or using Monster Timer ("the App"), you ("the User", "Parent", or "Guardian") acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms of this agreement. If you do not agree, please uninstall the App immediately.\n\n2. PURPOSE AND INTENDED USE\nMonster Timer is a parental control tool designed to help parents and guardians manage their children\'s YouTube Shorts screen time. The App is intended to be installed, configured, and supervised exclusively by a parent or legal guardian.\n\n3. PARENTAL RESPONSIBILITY\nYou acknowledge and agree that:\n• You are the parent or legal guardian of any child whose device this App is installed on.\n• You are solely responsible for configuring, monitoring, and supervising the App\'s use.\n• You are solely responsible for deciding appropriate screen time limits for your child.\n• The App is a supplementary tool and does not replace active parental supervision.\n• You are responsible for explaining the App\'s purpose to your child in an age-appropriate manner.\n\n4. ACCESSIBILITY SERVICE AND PERMISSIONS\nThe App requires Accessibility Service permissions and Display Over Other Apps permissions to function. You acknowledge that:\n• These permissions are granted voluntarily by you.\n• The App uses these permissions solely to detect YouTube Shorts usage and display the timer overlay.\n• The App does not collect, transmit, or store any personal data, browsing history, or screen content.\n• You understand the implications of granting these permissions on your child\'s device.\n\n5. NO WARRANTY\nThe App is provided "AS IS" without warranty of any kind, express or implied. The developer does not guarantee that:\n• The App will function without interruption or error.\n• The App will detect all instances of YouTube Shorts usage.\n• The timer or overlay will work correctly under all conditions.\n• The App will be compatible with all devices or Android versions.\n\n6. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\nTo the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, the developer shall not be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential, or punitive damages, including but not limited to:\n• Any distress caused to a child by the monster overlay.\n• Any failure of the App to limit screen time.\n• Any data loss or device malfunction.\n• Any unauthorized access resulting from granted permissions.\n\n7. CHILDREN\'S PRIVACY\nThe App does not knowingly collect personal information from children. All settings and usage data are stored locally on the device using encrypted storage and are never transmitted to any external server.\n\n8. CHANGES TO THIS AGREEMENT\nThe developer reserves the right to modify this agreement at any time. Continued use of the App after changes constitutes acceptance of the modified terms.\n\n9. GOVERNING LAW\nThis agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the jurisdiction in which the User resides.\n\nBy tapping "I Accept", you confirm that you are a parent or legal guardian and accept full responsibility for the use of this App.</string>
</resources>
